<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content=""Discover VibeNest's expert tips on social media management. Elevate your content creation game with insights from industry leaders. Join us today!""Visual Design in Social Media Management: Craft stunning visuals to boost engagement, enhance brand identity, and captivate your audience across platforms.""Master the art of copywriting for social media management. Boost engagement, drive conversions, and elevate your brand's online presence with compelling content.""Boost engagement with top-notch video production tailored for social media management. Drive impact and captivate audiences with compelling visual content.""Boost your social media management with eye-catching infographics: simplify data, enhance engagement, and communicate effectively in a visually compelling way.""Boost engagement with User-Generated Content in Social Media Management. Harness authentic posts to build community trust and drive interaction.""Optimize social media with analytics and reporting: track performance, gain insights, and refine your strategy for maximum engagement and growth.""Track and optimize social media success with performance metrics—measure engagement, reach, and ROI to maximize your strategy's effectiveness."Unlock deeper connections with Audience Insights in Social Media Management. Understand your followers, optimize content, and boost engagement effortlessly."Track user interactions on social media to boost engagement and optimize content strategy. Drive better results with effective engagement tracking in social media management."Boost engagement and optimize conversion rates with effective social media management. Transform interactions into measurable outcomes."Unlock insights in social media management with data visualization: track trends, measure engagement, and optimize strategy in just a glance."Boost brand loyalty with effective community engagement in social media management. Foster connections, drive interaction, and grow your online presence."Enhance customer service through effective social media management. Engage, respond, and build strong relationships with your audience seamlessly."Boost your brand with influencer collaboration! Streamline social media management and expand reach through strategic partnerships."Boost your brand with social media management by turning loyal customers into powerful advocates, driving engagement and organic growth.""Crisis Management in Social Media: Swiftly handle online turmoil, protect reputation, and maintain trust through strategic responses and proactive measures.""Boost engagement with efficient feedback collection in social media management. Gather insights, improve strategy, and connect better with your audience.""Optimize social media management with scheduling and automation tools to streamline content posting, boost engagement, and save time.""Optimize post timing in social media management to boost engagement and reach by scheduling content when your audience is most active."Effortlessly manage social media with automated responses. Boost engagement, save time, and ensure consistent communication across all platforms."Streamline social media management with seamless workflow integration, enhancing efficiency and collaboration for optimal content creation and scheduling.""Streamline your social media management with effective calendar planning. Schedule posts, track events, and stay organized for maximum engagement.""Optimize social media management with effective task delegation. Streamline workflows, enhance productivity, and achieve consistent online presence effortlessly.""Featured: Elevate your social media management with curated content, top posts, and highlights to boost engagement and visibility effortlessly.""Boost engagement with strategic advertising and promotion in social media management. Maximize reach, drive growth, and amplify your brand presence online.""Master campaign planning for social media management: strategize, engage, and drive results efficiently. Boost your brand with targeted content and analytics-driven decisions."Optimize your social media management with precise ad targeting, reaching the right audience and boosting engagement effectively.Optimize your social media management by mastering budget allocation. Allocate resources efficiently to maximize engagement, reach, and ROI on various platforms.Optimize your social media strategy with AB Testing. Compare posts, ads, and content to see what resonates best with your audience. Enhance engagement efficiently!"ROI Analysis in Social Media Management: Measure the impact of your social campaigns, optimize investments, and boost engagement effectively."">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo-512--512px.png"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.fc3e64e05fb3787a50057876551b0cf53 p,.fc3e64e05fb3787a50057876551b0cf53 a,.fc3e64e05fb3787a50057876551b0cf53 span,.fc3e64e05fb3787a50057876551b0cf53 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
.f157025451393b3437fab4a7ecab76cd1{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
.a35eaf7eb4647e6bfd5fb4f7889b09712 p,.a35eaf7eb4647e6bfd5fb4f7889b09712 span,.a35eaf7eb4647e6bfd5fb4f7889b09712 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.5px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.nav-link{
color: #873c87;

}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.3px;
padding-right:8.3px;
padding-top:5px;
padding-bottom:5.4px;
}
a:hover{
color:;background:!important;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.1px 29.7px;
border-radius: 0;
}
footer{
background:#0b0b0b;
color:#ffffff;
}
.ve12427737688049b8b467045d6d7ad36:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.3px 49.6px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.a35eaf7eb4647e6bfd5fb4f7889b09712 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.fc3e64e05fb3787a50057876551b0cf53 a,.a35eaf7eb4647e6bfd5fb4f7889b09712 a{
color:#131313!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo-512--512px.png" src="img/logo-512--512px.png"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="d-flex navbar-nav ml-auto align-items-center"><li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/news.html"  >News</a></li>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd nav-link" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">VibeNest Content Creation Weblog</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/index.html"  >VibeNest Content Creation Weblog</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/visual-design.html"  >Visual Design</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/copywriting.html"  >Copywriting</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/video-production.html"  >Video Production</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/infographics.html"  >Infographics</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/usergenerated-content.html"  >UserGenerated Content</a>
  
<li class="dropdown nav-item ">
<a class="nav-link v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd dropdown-toggle" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/analytics-and-reporting.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Analytics and Reporting</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/analytics-and-reporting.html"  >Analytics and Reporting</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/performance-metrics.html"  >Performance Metrics</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/audience-insights.html"  >Audience Insights</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/engagement-tracking.html"  >Engagement Tracking</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/conversion-rates.html"  >Conversion Rates</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/data-visualization.html"  >Data Visualization</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd nav-link dropdown-toggle" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/community-engagement.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Community Engagement</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/community-engagement.html"  >Community Engagement</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/customer-service.html"  >Customer Service</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/influencer-collaboration.html"  >Influencer Collaboration</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/brand-advocacy.html"  >Brand Advocacy</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/crisis-management.html"  >Crisis Management</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/feedback-collection.html"  >Feedback Collection</a>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/scheduling-and-automation.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Scheduling and Automation</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/scheduling-and-automation.html"  >Scheduling and Automation</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/post-timing-optimization.html"  >Post Timing Optimization</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/automated-responses.html"  >Automated Responses</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/workflow-integration.html"  >Workflow Integration</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/calendar-planning.html"  >Calendar Planning</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/task-delegation.html"  >Task Delegation</a>
  
<li class="dropdown  nav-item">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/featured.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Featured</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/featured.html"  >Featured</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/advertising-and-promotion.html"  >Advertising and Promotion</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/campaign-planning.html"  >Campaign Planning</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/ad-targeting.html"  >Ad Targeting</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/budget-allocation.html"  >Budget Allocation</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/ab-testing.html"  >AB Testing</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/roi-analysis.html"  >ROI Analysis</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" rel=nofollow href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for VibeNest</h1>
<p>At VibeNest one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by VibeNest and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: </p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in VibeNest. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, VibeNest, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>VibeNest follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of VibeNest.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on VibeNest, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that VibeNest has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>VibeNest's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>VibeNest does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
VibeNest</br>
461-960-7539</br>
1446  Valley Road</br>
Fort Wayne, IN, 46802</br>
United States</br>
</br>
SofiaLove@outlook.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 container pt-5" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="v952a26c48eae0f0b2c79a5ca3462bddd" href="https://socialmediasites.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
